[
    {
        "question": "What models are included in the Porsche 718 series?",
        "answer": "The Porsche 718 series include 718 Cayman, 718 Boxster, 718 Cayman Style Edition, 718 Boxster Style Edition, 718 Cayman S, 718 Boxster S, 718 Cayman GTS 4.0, 718 Boxster GTS 4.0, 718 Cayman GT4 RS, and 718 Spyder RS."
    },
    {
        "question": "What models are included in the Porsche 911 series?",
        "answer": "The Porsche 911 series include 911 Carrera, 911 Carrera GTS, 911 Carrera 4 GTS, 911 Carrera T, 911 Carrera Cabriolet, 911 Carrera GTS Cabriolet, 911 Carrera 4 GTS Cabriolet, 911 Carrera T Cabriolet, 911 Targa 4 GTS, 911 Turbo 50 Years, 911 Turbo, 911 Turbo Cabriolet, 911 Turbo S, 911 Turbo S Cabriolet, 911 GT3, 911 GT3 with Touring Package, 911 GT3 RS, 911 Dakar, and 911 S/T."
    },
    {
        "question": "What models are included in the Porsche taycan series?",
        "answer": "The Porsche taycan series include Taycan, Taycan 4, Taycan 4S, Taycan GTS, Taycan Turbo, Taycan Turbo S, Taycan Turbo GT, Taycan Turbo GT with Weissach package, Taycan 4 Cross Turismo, Taycan 4S Cross Turismo, Taycan Turbo Cross Turismo, Taycan Turbo S Cross Turismo, Taycan Sport Turismo, Taycan 4S Sport Turismo, Taycan GTS Sport Turismo, Taycan Turbo Sport Turismo, and Taycan Turbo S Sport Turismo."
    },
    {
        "question": "What models are included in the Porsche panamera series?",
        "answer": "The Porsche panamera series include Panamera, Panamera 4, Panamera 4 E-Hybrid, Panamera 4S E-Hybrid, Panamera GTS, Panamera Turbo E-Hybrid, Panamera Turbo S E-Hybrid, Panamera 4 E-Hybrid Executive, and Panamera Turbo S E-Hybrid Executive."
    },
    {
        "question": "What models are included in the Porsche macan series?",
        "answer": "The Porsche macan series include Macan Electric, Macan 4 Electric, Macan 4S Electric, Macan Turbo Electric, Macan, Macan T, Macan S, and Macan GTS."
    },
    {
        "question": "What models are included in the Porsche cayenne series?",
        "answer": "The Porsche cayenne series include Cayenne, Cayenne E-Hybrid, Cayenne S, Cayenne S E-Hybrid, Cayenne GTS, Cayenne Turbo E-Hybrid, Cayenne Coup\u00e9, Cayenne E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9, Cayenne S Coup\u00e9, Cayenne S E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9, Cayenne GTS Coup\u00e9, Cayenne Turbo E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9, and Cayenne Turbo E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9 with GT-Package."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Cayman",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Cayman. It has a horsepower of 300. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Boxster",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Boxster. It has a horsepower of 300. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Cayman Style Edition",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Cayman Style Edition. It has a horsepower of 300. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Boxster Style Edition",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Boxster Style Edition. It has a horsepower of 300. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Cayman S",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Cayman S. It has a horsepower of 350. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Boxster S",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Boxster S. It has a horsepower of 350. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Cayman GTS 4.0",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Cayman GTS 4.0. It has a horsepower of 400. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Boxster GTS 4.0",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Boxster GTS 4.0. It has a horsepower of 400. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Cayman GT4 RS",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Cayman GT4 RS. It has a horsepower of 500. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 718 Spyder RS",
        "answer": "The model is called 718 Spyder RS. It has a horsepower of 500. This is a roadster vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Carrera",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Carrera. It has a horsepower of 394. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Carrera GTS",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Carrera GTS. It has a horsepower of 485. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Carrera 4 GTS",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Carrera 4 GTS. It has a horsepower of 485. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Carrera T",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Carrera T. It has a horsepower of 394. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Carrera Cabriolet",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Carrera Cabriolet. It has a horsepower of 394. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Carrera GTS Cabriolet",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Carrera GTS Cabriolet. It has a horsepower of 485. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Carrera 4 GTS Cabriolet",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Carrera 4 GTS Cabriolet. It has a horsepower of 485. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Carrera T Cabriolet",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Carrera T Cabriolet. It has a horsepower of 394. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Targa 4 GTS",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Targa 4 GTS. It has a horsepower of 485. This is a targa vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Turbo 50 Years",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Turbo 50 Years. It has a horsepower of 650. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Turbo",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Turbo. It has a horsepower of 580. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Turbo Cabriolet",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Turbo Cabriolet. It has a horsepower of 580. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Turbo S",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Turbo S. It has a horsepower of 650. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Turbo S Cabriolet",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Turbo S Cabriolet. It has a horsepower of 650. This is a cabriolet vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 GT3",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 GT3. It has a horsepower of 510. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 GT3 with Touring Package",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 GT3 with Touring Package. It has a horsepower of 510. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual and pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 GT3 RS",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 GT3 RS. It has a horsepower of 525. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 Dakar",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 Dakar. It has a horsepower of 480. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model 911 S/T",
        "answer": "The model is called 911 S/T. It has a horsepower of 525. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include manual. It has seating for 2 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan. It has a horsepower of 408. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan 4",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan 4. It has a horsepower of 408. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan 4S",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan 4S. It has a horsepower of 544. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan GTS",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan GTS. It has a horsepower of 700. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan Turbo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan Turbo. It has a horsepower of 884. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan Turbo S",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan Turbo S. It has a horsepower of 952. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan Turbo GT",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan Turbo GT. It has a horsepower of 1034. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan Turbo GT with Weissach package",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan Turbo GT with Weissach package. It has a horsepower of 1034. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan 4 Cross Turismo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan 4 Cross Turismo. It has a horsepower of 435. This is a crossturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan 4S Cross Turismo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan 4S Cross Turismo. It has a horsepower of 598. This is a crossturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan Turbo Cross Turismo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan Turbo Cross Turismo. It has a horsepower of 884. This is a crossturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan Turbo S Cross Turismo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan Turbo S Cross Turismo. It has a horsepower of 952. This is a crossturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan Sport Turismo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan Sport Turismo. It has a horsepower of 408. This is a sportturismo vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan 4S Sport Turismo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan 4S Sport Turismo. It has a horsepower of 544. This is a sportturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan GTS Sport Turismo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan GTS Sport Turismo. It has a horsepower of 700. This is a sportturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan Turbo Sport Turismo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan Turbo Sport Turismo. It has a horsepower of 884. This is a sportturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Taycan Turbo S Sport Turismo",
        "answer": "The model is called Taycan Turbo S Sport Turismo. It has a horsepower of 952. This is a sportturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include 2speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Panamera",
        "answer": "The model is called Panamera. It has a horsepower of 353. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Panamera 4",
        "answer": "The model is called Panamera 4. It has a horsepower of 353. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Panamera 4 E-Hybrid",
        "answer": "The model is called Panamera 4 E-Hybrid. It has a horsepower of 470. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Panamera 4S E-Hybrid",
        "answer": "The model is called Panamera 4S E-Hybrid. It has a horsepower of 544. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Panamera GTS",
        "answer": "The model is called Panamera GTS. It has a horsepower of 500. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Panamera Turbo E-Hybrid",
        "answer": "The model is called Panamera Turbo E-Hybrid. It has a horsepower of 680. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Panamera Turbo S E-Hybrid",
        "answer": "The model is called Panamera Turbo S E-Hybrid. It has a horsepower of 782. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Panamera 4 E-Hybrid Executive",
        "answer": "The model is called Panamera 4 E-Hybrid Executive. It has a horsepower of 470. This is a executive vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Panamera Turbo S E-Hybrid Executive",
        "answer": "The model is called Panamera Turbo S E-Hybrid Executive. It has a horsepower of 782. This is a granturismo vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Macan Electric",
        "answer": "The model is called Macan Electric. It has a horsepower of 360. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a rearwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. The transmission options include 1speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Macan 4 Electric",
        "answer": "The model is called Macan 4 Electric. It has a horsepower of 408. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. The transmission options include 1speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Macan 4S Electric",
        "answer": "The model is called Macan 4S Electric. It has a horsepower of 516. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. The transmission options include 1speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Macan Turbo Electric",
        "answer": "The model is called Macan Turbo Electric. It has a horsepower of 639. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses electro as fuel. The transmission options include 1speed. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Macan",
        "answer": "The model is called Macan. It has a horsepower of 265. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Macan T",
        "answer": "The model is called Macan T. It has a horsepower of 265. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Macan S",
        "answer": "The model is called Macan S. It has a horsepower of 380. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Macan GTS",
        "answer": "The model is called Macan GTS. It has a horsepower of 440. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. The transmission options include pdk. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne. It has a horsepower of 353. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne E-Hybrid",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne E-Hybrid. It has a horsepower of 470. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne S",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne S. It has a horsepower of 474. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne S E-Hybrid",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne S E-Hybrid. It has a horsepower of 519. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne GTS",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne GTS. It has a horsepower of 500. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne Turbo E-Hybrid",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne Turbo E-Hybrid. It has a horsepower of 739. This is a suv-cuv vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne Coup\u00e9",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne Coup\u00e9. It has a horsepower of 353. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9. It has a horsepower of 470. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne S Coup\u00e9",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne S Coup\u00e9. It has a horsepower of 474. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne S E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne S E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9. It has a horsepower of 519. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne GTS Coup\u00e9",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne GTS Coup\u00e9. It has a horsepower of 500. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses benzine as fuel. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne Turbo E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne Turbo E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9. It has a horsepower of 739. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me a brief introduction to Porsche model Cayenne Turbo E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9 with GT-Package",
        "answer": "The model is called Cayenne Turbo E-Hybrid Coup\u00e9 with GT-Package. It has a horsepower of 739. This is a coupe vehicle. It features a allwheel drive system. The car uses hybrid as fuel. It is designed for everyday performance. The transmission options include tiptronic. It has seating for 4-5 passengers."
    }
]